pdfconverter.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy - PDF Converter

BC LTD. (“Our Company”) is committed to make your visit to pdfconverter.com an experience that is as interesting and enjoyable as possible. Our Privacy Policy below is geared towards understanding that you are a guest at our site and should be treated as such.

Our privacy policy complies with UK law accordingly implemented, containing that required by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).  
We are obliged to inform you about your rights and our duties to you concerning the processing and controlling your personal data.

## Use of Personal Information

Any information you submit through Our Company’s web site will be held in the strictest confidence. In no way will your personal information ever be shared with any third party without your consent. Be assured that we do not sell your name and address lists. If you choose to receive information from us, each message will also include instructions on how to “unsubscribe” from future mailings should you wish to cancel.

The only information we automatically collect is that related to the use of our website. This information is anonymous and is gathered through our servers’ log files. These log files record generic information, such as the number of visits our web site receives, the types of browsers used and the number of files downloaded, but never personal information. This log file information allows us to create better content aimed at our viewer’s preferences.

Our Company does not collect information that personally identifies individuals except when individuals provide such specific information on a voluntary basis. Such information will be kept strictly confidential. There may be occasions where specific personal information is requested before an individual can enter certain sections of Our Company’s site or for participation in a certain program. For example, registration may be required to participate in a contest.

When you buy a product or service from us, use our online conversion tool or otherwise agree to our terms and conditions, a contract is formed between us. In order to complete a purchase or use our online tools we must process your personal information. We need to use your personal information to sell products to you and provide with our services. That information is entered by you and used only for purposes of the contract. We will continue to process your information until the contract between us is terminated by either party under the terms of the contract.

If there is a legitimate interest, either to you or to us, we may process your personal information. When we do that, we first carefully consider whether the same objective could be completed in other ways, whether that processing (or not processing) might cause you harm, whether you expect us to collect your data, and whether you would find it reasonable to do that.

As for your payment information, you are transferred to our payment provider and although the purchase page looks like a part of our website, it is controlled by our providers. Our employees don’t have access to your payment information.

On some occasions, we must be legally obliged to process your personal information in order to comply with a statutory obligation.

## Complaint about content on our website

If you have complaints about our website, send us an email to [compliance@pdfconverter.com](mailto:compliance@pdfconverter.com) to investigate your complaint.

When you contact our support team whether by telephone or by email, we collect the data you give us so we can reply to you and provide you with the information you need. We record your message and our reply in order to improve the efficiency of our business and customer support. If your message requires us to contact some other person, we may give to that person some of the information contained in your message.

## Use of Data Collection

All products and all studies, reports, analyses and other data, information or materials created in whole or part using data obtained from [www.pdfconverter.com](https://www.pdfconverter.com/) shall be and remain the sole property of Our Company. None of the data will be returned to you. As it is proprietary information, Our Company intends to keep the data confidential. Furthermore, Our Company intends to use the data for the purpose of developing and enhancing software, future versions of the software and/or related or similar software.

The voluntary policies that Our Company intends to follow to maintain the confidentiality of the data include sharing the data only with employees, agents, consultants, or officers of Our Company with a need to know. PLEASE NOTE, HOWEVER, that Our Company’s handling or treatment of the data is entirely voluntary and, therefore, OUR COMPANY WILL HAVE NO LIABILITY TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PARTY FOR FAILURE TO KEEP THE DATA CONFIDENTIAL OR TO OTHERWISE HANDLE OR TREAT THE DATA IN ANY MANNER.

Data may be processed outside the European Union

Our website is hosted in Canada. We may also use outsourced services in countries outside the European Union from time to time in other aspects of our business. Accordingly, data obtained within the UK or any other country could be processed outside the European Union. For example, some of the software our website uses may have been developed in the United States of America or in Australia. We use the following safeguards with respect to data transferred outside the European Union:

– the processor is within the same corporate group as our business or organisation and abides by the same binding corporate rules regarding data processing

– the data protection clauses in our contracts with data processors include transfer clauses written by or approved by a supervisory authority in the European Union [, specifically that in the country of Germany]

– we comply with a code of conduct approved by a supervisory authority in the European Union

– we are certified under an approved certification mechanism as provided for in the GDPR

– both our organisation and the processor are public authorities between whom there is either a legally binding agreement or administrative arrangements approved by a supervisory authority in the European Union relating to protection of your information

## Use of Cookies

As of February 1st 2009, [www.pdfconverter.com](https://www.pdfconverter.com/) does not use a feature of your browser called a “cookie”, only on our blog.

However, Our Company does reserve the right to use cookies in the future on the whole website. Cookies, by themselves, are not able to extract any personal information from you. The cookie automatically identifies your computer – but not you – to our servers when you visit our site. Cookies allow us to personalize our site for you and to provide you with information that fits your needs and desires.

Unless you specifically tell us, Our Company will never know who you are, even though we may assign your computer a cookie. Also, should we decide to employ cookies in the future, we will inform you.

## Access to your own information

### Access to your personal information

At any time, you may review or update personally identifiable information that we hold about you, by sending us email to compliance@pdfconverter.com. To obtain a copy of any information that is not provided on our website you may send us a request at the same email. After receiving the request, we will tell you when we expect to provide you with the information, and whether we require any fee for providing it to you.

### Removal of your information

If you wish us to remove personally identifiable information from our website, you may contact us at [compliance@pdfconverter.com](mailto:compliance@pdfconverter.com). This may limit the service we can provide to you.

### Verification of your information

When we receive any request to access, edit or delete personal identifiable information we shall first take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or otherwise taking any action. This is important to safeguard your information.

### Security measures

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to encrypt the information you enter on our Site in order to protect its security during transmission to and from our Site. When storing information, we protect its security by encryption and pseudonymization of critical data. When we process credit card information and payments, the credit card is subject to tokenization and strong security measures. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures require us in some cases to request proof of identity before disclosing personal information to you. To protect against unauthorised access to your account and information, we implement session management, login expiration mechanisms and the option of using 2-factor authentication for User Area access. As an additional safety measure, be sure to sign off when you finish using your account and your computer. Although we take all these measures to maintain the safety and security of your personal information, please note that no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be secure. Consequently, please note that we cannot fully guarantee the security of any personal information that you transfer over the Internet to us.

### Retention period for personal data

Except as otherwise mentioned in this privacy notice, we keep your personal information only for as long as required by us to provide you with the services you have requested, to comply with other law, including for the period demanded by our tax authorities or to support a claim or defence in court.

### Compliance with the law

Our privacy policy has been compiled so as to comply with the law of every country or legal jurisdiction in which we aim to do business. If you think it fails to satisfy the law of your jurisdiction, we should like to hear from you. However, ultimately it is your choice as to whether you wish to use our website.

### Contact us

Our Company knows that your privacy is very important to you. If you have any questions or complaints regarding our policy, feel free to contact us at [compliance@pdfconverter.com](mailto:compliance@pdfconverter.com). If a dispute is not settled then we hope you will agree to attempt to resolve it by engaging in good faith with us in a process of mediation or arbitration.

Our Company reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement from time to time. You should print the copy of the current privacy statement because the privacy rules that apply to you are those available on the date when you visited our website.
